bayphoto.com 2017-02-26

# Privacy Policy – Bay Photo Lab

Bay Photo Lab believes in the importance of safeguarding your privacy on bayphoto.com and [my.bayphoto.com](https://my.bayphoto.com/). This Bay Photo Lab Privacy Policy only applies to products or services provided, as well as information obtained, from the Site. Please read the following policy to understand how your private information will be handled. If you have questions concerning this policy, please contact Joy Sanchez at [joy@bayphoto.com](mailto:joy@bayphoto.com).

**Bay Photo Lab collects information in several ways:**

  * We gather information when you sign up for an account. During that process we will ask you for a variety of personal information we need to be able to identify you and your account.
  * After you receive your account number, and you email or call in to ask us questions, we will ask for your account number, order numbers, etc.
  * When you inquire about our site or the services we provide, we will likely ask you for information related to your account, account number, order number, or other information.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that communication.
  * We always strive to maintain the highest level of accuracy in the information we retain about you. If you ever feel that any inaccurate or inappropriate information has been obtained or transmitted through the use of this Site, please contact [joy@bayphoto.com](mailto:joy@bayphoto.com).

“Cookies” are a small amount of data that are sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. “Cookies” allow quicker and easier access to your account information, they help us monitor traffic on the Site, and they also help us analyze how people use our Site, so we can make changes to improve the customer experience at bayphoto.com. "Cookies" can be easily deleted from your web browser by going to the browsers control panel and clearing "Cookies".

We collect information from our customers to simplify order entry and order tracking. We may do research on what preferences you show when you’re using our site, so that we can then offer you promotions based on the needs you’ve sought to fulfill at bayphoto.com. Bay Photo Lab will absolutely not share this information with any other company without your approval.

When you are on the Bay Photo Lab web site and you are asked for information, you are sharing that information with Bay Photo Lab. The information practices of other Web sites linked to our Sites are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

We will not disclose any of your personal information unless you give us permission, or when we determine, in good faith, that the law requires it, or under other special circumstances.

**The following describes some of the ways that your information may be disclosed:**

We may disclose this information if we feel it is necessary to bring legal action because someone has violated the Bay Photo Lab Terms and Conditions or in cases where not disclosing that information could cause injury to Bay Photo Lab’s rights or property, to Bay Photo Lab Site users or customers, or anyone who could be harmed by the failure to make such a disclosure. We may disclose or access account information when, in good faith, we believe the law requires it as well as for other purposes we feel are necessary to maintain, service, and improve services to our customers.

Through our [my.bayphoto.com](https://my.bayphoto.com/) secure site you can modify your personal information. You may also contact our Customer Service Department or our Accounting Department if you wish to view, edit or delete your personal information from our database. 

Our customer’s privacy is of the highest level of importance. We will not sell any information provided to us by our customers. We will transfer your credit card number, bank account number or other personal information to the appropriate credit card company or bank in order to process any online payments. 

Your Bay Photo Lab Account Information and Bay Photo Lab Profile are password-protected on a secure site so that you can have access to your personal information.

In order to maintain security from your personal computer, always sign out of your Bay Photo account at [my.bayphoto.com](https://my.bayphoto.com/) any time you leave your computer and have finished your work.

No data transmission over the internet is 100% secure. As a result, any information you divulge in the use of this site (as with any site that is non-secure) by posting a message or using email, potentially could be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties for their own purposes. While we strive to protect your personal information, Bay Photo Lab cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose information online, that information is accessible to other users. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information.  Always use caution whenever you are online.
